export default data = [
  {
      question: "All the flights to and from Kaohsiung were _____ because of the heavy thunderstorm.",
      options: ["advised","disclosed","cancelled","benefited"],
      correct_option: "cancelled"
  },
  {
      question: "The woman told the truth to her lawyer without ____ because he was the only person she could rely on.",
      options: ["reservation","combination","impression","foundation"],
      correct_option: "reservation"
  },
  {
      question: "The man was severely injured in last weekend’s tragic car accident and died _____ afterwards.",
      options: ["mostly","shortly","easily","hardly"],
      correct_option: "shortly"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Smith’s work in Taiwan is just _____. He will go back to the U.S. next month.",
      options: ["liberal","rural","conscious","temporary"],
      correct_option: "temporary"
  },
  {
      question: "Helen _____ with anger when she saw her boyfriend kissing an attractive girl.",
      options: ["collided","exploded","relaxed","defeated"],
      correct_option: "exploded"
  },
  {
      question: "Dr. Liu’s new book is a collection of his _____ of the daily life of tribal people in Africa. ",
      options: ["observations","interferences","preventions","substitutions"],
      correct_option: "observations"
  },
  {
      question: "The young couple decided to ______ their wedding until all the details were well taken care of.",
      options: ["announce","maintain","postpone","simplify"],
      correct_option: "postpone"
  },
  {
      question: "The conflicts between John and his teacher made it difficult for the teacher to judge his performance _____.",
      options: ["objectively","painfully","excitedly","intimately"],
      correct_option: "objectively"
  },
  {
      question: "Living in a highly _____ society, you definitely have to arm yourself with as much knowledge as possible.",
      options: ["tolerant","permanent","favorable","competitive"],
      correct_option: "competitive"
  },
  {
      question: "The 70-year-old professor sued the university for age _____, because his teaching contract had not been renewed.",
      options: ["possession","commitment","discrimination","employment"],
      correct_option: "discrimination"
  },
  {
      question: "Kevin burst into tears _____ because his teacher punished him in front of the whole class.",
      options: ["on the side","on the spot","on any account","on the mark"],
      correct_option: "on the spot"
  },
  {
      question: "As soon as the couple realized that they didn’t love each other anymore, they _____.",
      options: ["fell off","cut in","broke up","stood by"],
      correct_option: "broke up"
  },
  {
      question: "The power workers had to work _____ to repair the power lines since the whole city was in the dark.",
      options: ["around the clock","in the extreme","on the house","in the majority"],
      correct_option: "around the clock"
  },
  {
      question: "After retirement, Mr. Wang _____ ice skating, which he had always loved but had not had time for.",
      options: ["appealed to","took to","related to","saw to"],
      correct_option: "took to"
  },
  {
      question: "Why do we have to _____ Sue’s selfish behavior? We have to teach her to care for others.",
      options: ["get over with","hang out with","make up with","put up with"],
      correct_option: "put up with"
  },
]
